--Morning!
--Good morning!
"Class 2-4"
--It's been a while.
--Happy new year.
You, too.
Shido? Why are you spaced out?
Huh? Oh. There's a lot on my mind.
Spirits were humans in the beginning?
Oh, hold up.
I mean, I know I was,
so I figured the others were, too.
Though now that Raziel's incomplete,
I doubt I can look into it again.
I never could find out much
about the Spirit of Origin.
Having said that,
my power isn't completely gone.
I think I'll be able to hinder Westcott
from using Future Entry.
Artemisia Ashcroft is
the British Anti-Spirit Team's ace.
As far as Wizards go,
she's way better than me.
But I always thought she hated DEM,
so I wonder why she joined Westcott?
I hope everyone had a wonderful break!
Today starts our third semester
in a brand new year.
My birthday's not till March, though.
How old do you think I am?
Since I refuse to turn "thirty,"
I'm gonna call it "sirty."
Clever, right?
T-Tammie?
So now when you speak to me,
please refer to me as "Sir."
S-Sir! Yes, Sir!
Sir! Did something happen, Sir?
Oh, nothing much. Just my best friend
Eri deciding on her wedding date.
So happy for her...
Yet I'm still unclaimed. It seems
the god of tying the knot hates me.
Okay! Let's take attendance!
"Class 2-4"
--Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Sir! You're not okay, Sir!
Sir! You need a break, Sir!
Sir! That's so lame, Sir!
No, no, it's all right!
But if a demon appeared to grant
a wish in exchange for my soul,
I might just say:
"Send an asteroid at Japan, please!"
Abracadabra! Drop on asteroid on me!
--An asteroid?!
--Did Tammie summon one?!
--Tammie!
Shido, that's...
Shido, head to temp command.
Huh? You mean...?
Yeah. It's a Spirit.
The Spirits?
They're on standby like you asked.
What happened?
Check this out.
Something fell in the schoolyard, right?
The same thing happened in
all of these locations simultaneously.
Everywhere, simultaneously?
DEM and other country's
Anti-Spirit Teams were hit, too.
It's possible they targeted
Spirit power and magic.
Targeted? Who?
Her?
Yeah. It's a Spirit
we've never seen before.
We're giving her the code name, "Zodiac."
This video is from three hours ago.
DEM discovered Zodiac first.
We noticed odd movements from
DEM ships and probed the area.
Westcott most likely found her
using Beelzebub.
Though incomplete,
he must have managed it somehow.
Segva.
So that's her Angel?
Yes, "Michael."
Jabbing that key into things can lock
and close off their abilities.
Lataib.
An attack?
It's another of Michael's powers.
The key is put into "space"
and opens up something
resembling a warp gate.
She's able to control
where the portals will exit.
I see! So the asteroid at school...!
Correct. It's how Zodiac
carried out her attack on Earth.
She opened up gates in space
and tossed DEM ship debris through.
She was probably upset at being
woken from her nice little nap.
What will we do? Go to space?
Don't worry. I've got an idea.
It's a 3D projection.
If we project it into space
along with a camera,
you can talk to her
like you're actually there.
Now then, it's time for long-distance love
between Earth and space!
H-Hey. Hi there.
Kotori, help! My head! It's blown off!
Relax! It's still attached.
Calm down! I'm not an enemy.
Hold on!
I...!
Talk about aggressive!
I've died five times already!
Mm. I didn't think
she would be this violent.
It's a good thing
we went with a projection.
Strange. Why aren't you dead yet?
Finally, we're talking.
It's 'cuz I'm being projected here.
Projected? Hmm... That's strange.
Would you mind telling me your name?
Mukuro. Mukuro Hoshimiya.
I see. I...
"1. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be friends."
"2. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be lovers."
"3. I'm Shido Itsuka, your future husband.
I'm gonna make your body crave me."
"1. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be friends."
"2. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be lovers."
"3. I'm Shido Itsuka, your future husband. I'm gonna make your body crave me."
Your choices, everyone!
"1. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be friends."
"2. I'm Shido Itsuka. Let's be lovers."
"3. I'm Shido Itsuka, your future husband. I'm gonna make your body crave me."
I see. Three.
Yeah. One and two work,
but let's go on the offensive.
We haven't seen her happiness
move either way yet.
We need to get a reaction.
Shido, do three.
Three?!
Whatever happens,
it's not like you're gonna die.
We wanna see what sort of
reaction it gets. Hurry up.
I'm Shido Itsuka, your future husband.
I-I'm gonna make your body... crave me.
Shido Itsuka, huh?
That's it?!
How are her levels looking?
No changes across the board.
Levels are so flat, it's scary.
What is your goal? Why did you come here?
I go around trying
to help Spirits like you.
Ratatoskr?
There are nine others like Muku
whom you've already helped?
Yeah. So can you come to the surface
and let me seal your power?
I refuse.
While I understand your objective,
Muku does not need your help.
I'm content floating up here.
B-But DEM might come attack you again!
That scrap metal? Come as they may,
they're hardly an enemy.
But the surface is lots of fun.
It's sad up here by yourself.
It's not an issue. Muku doesn't feel sad.
No need to act tough.
It's not like that.
Muku doesn't feel loneliness.
Nor sadness, anger, excitement,
delight, joy, nor love.
Muku has locked her heart.
Locked... your heart?
Why do that?
I wonder why? It was so long ago,
it's hard to remember.
Muku wants for nothing to touch her heart.
That's why Muku's here,
where no one can reach.
That's... But that's so sad!
Please! Come down to Earth
so you can be happy!
You don't get to decide
what makes Muku happy.
Perhaps there are Spirits you've saved.
But Muku is Muku.
Leave me out of it.
Th-That's...
Supposing you seal my power,
can you guarantee Muku will be safe?
Would not the Spirits you "save"
be exposed to greater peril?
Shido, I tire hearing of this hypocrisy.
If people don't learn to leave
Muku alone, let's see...
I shall use Michael
to stop this planet's spin.
Goodbye, Shido. May we not meet again.
Segva.
The image was cut!
The camera's not responding!
Ow!
You're that depressed
over getting shot down?
I understand her view.
If not for us,
some Spirits might've had
better futures and be better off.
But don't forget:
Spirits cause huge disasters, too.
A power that dangerous looming above us
is something we can't ignore.
But if we leave her alone,
she won't do anything.
Even if we don't, what about DEM?
If DEM beats Mukuro,
Westcott will gain her power.
And if they fail,
Mukuro will devastate the Earth.
We have no choice but to seal
Mukuro's powers before DEM gets her.
You're right. I guess we've gotta.
Well? What are they saying?
Request. Stop pushing me.
Shh! They'll hear!
What are you guys doing?
Mm. Sorry. We didn't mean to eavesdrop.
Don't apologize! In fact, it's only
natural we're worried about Darling!
We may have overheard a little.
Is there any way we can help?
There's just one option:
Use her Angel to open
the very same heart she closed.
In other words,
use Michael on Mukuro again.
I see! But we can't do that
without going to her in person.
Don't worry. I've got a plan.
--Huh?
What good timing.
There's something I wanna show you.
Fraxinus' bridge?
No, it's different than before.
Yup. It's a new model with
everything upgraded: Fraxinus Excelsior!
Space is a cakewalk for her!
Hello, Fraxinus. How goes it?
Welcome, Kotori. It's good to see you.
Wha--?!
How rude, Shido.
Were I a Spirit,
my happiness would drop.
It's Fraxinus' AI. The upgrades
made it able to converse.
My call sign is MARIA. It's a pleasure
to work with you again, Shido.
Yeah. It's a pleasure, MARIA.
So? How long till we can depart, MARIA?
Roughly 90 minutes.
I've restored everyone's customizations,
but please confirm them individually.
--Roger!
Also, please limit personal goods
brought on the bridge.
You do not need straw dolls
or anime figures.
You're kidding!
You never complained before!
Because I couldn't speak.
Also, please refrain from
calling ex-wives and call girls.
--Eh?!
Cameras are not to be used
to spy on past lovers.
No way!
You guys were using
Fraxinus for such things?
--No!
--As if!
--We'd never!
Kotori, an on-base visitor
is asking for a meeting.
Meeting?
It's Chairman Elliot Woodman.
The chairman?!
You know him, Shido?
No, the name rings no bells.
Hey. It's been a while.
You're...!
I remember! You asked for directions.
That I did.
Allow me to reintroduce myself:
I'm Elliot Baldwin Woodman.
Kotori? Who is he?
He's the chairman of Ratatoskr's
decision-making round table.
He's it's head and founder.
Shido Itsuka, you have my thanks.
Thank you for saving so many Spirits.
Uh, no, thank you.
Without Ratatoskr, I'd get nowhere.
I've got questions.
First off, Elliot Baldwin Woodman...
That is you, right?
Yes.
Tell me: As one of DEM's
founding members,
what's your goal behind saving
Spirits, when 30 years ago,
it was you who first manifested them?
They manifested... Spirits?
If you hadn't manifested
Spirits and made DEM,
we wouldn't have had
to go through all this.
What exactly are you plotting?
I see. You have the power
to look up anything, don't you?
You must have done so to me long ago.
I never meant to hide anything.
Yes, I founded DEM along with
Isaac Westcott and Ellen Mathers
hoping to utilize the power of Spirits.
But laying eyes upon the Spirit of Origin
changed me forever.
I left DEM with Karen Mathers here,
who felt the same as me.
Mathers...
She is Ellen Mathers' little sister,
though Ellen looks like the younger one.
Anyway, I dedicated my life
to the protection of Spirits,
despite making enemies of Ike and Ellen.
What exactly happened?
Love. Love happened.
Love?
The moment I saw the Spirit of Origin,
she stole my heart away.
That's why I can't stand seeing
other Spirits like her in pain--
as silly a reason as it seems.
I don't think it's silly.
Actually, I'm kinda glad Ratatoskr
was founded by someone like you.
Thank you. Sorry, but can I get
a better look at your face?
Huh? Um, sure.
I see. You look like the boy after all...
Huh?
Emergency! Confirming DEM airship above!
We're under attack!
You're kidding! How did they find us?
Beelzebub!
Commander Itsuka, take the Fraxinus.
Once I deal with things here,
I'll escape another way.
Roger that. Stay safe.
Take care of the Spirits, Shido Itsuka.
And please, save Zodiac.
Just how many enemies are there?
I don't know, so let's hurry!
That's...!
Westcott...
Well, well.
I finally tracked down
Elliot and you guys show up.
It's lovely to see you again,
but I need you bunch to behave.
I'll play with you after Elliot.
"Episode 04:
'Space Spirit.'"
Once upon a time,
there was a man named Shido Itsuka.
Who awaits Shido, Momotaro,
and Little Red Riding Hood at the ball?
Next time: "Fairy Tale."
"Episode 04: 'Fairy Tale.'"
The emperor has no clothes.